ladyboygloryhole.com 2018-05-14

# www.ladyboygloryhole.com- Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to the following Web site: www.ladyboygloryhole.com

Information Collection.

We do not collect any client infroamtion.

Registration and Order Forms

To use, purchase, or order services on our Site, a user must complete an on-line form. The form requires a user to provide the billing company with certain contact information. This information is used to purchase products and services, manage the user’s account, and/or ship products. If the billing company has trouble processing an order or otherwise need to contact a user, the contact information is used to get in touch with the user.

Law Enforcement

We will cooperate with law enforcement authorities, private-party litigants, and others seeking information about our end users to the extent required by applicable law. Examples of such cooperation include compliance with discovery requests, subpoenas, court orders and writs. 

Security

Secure Socket Ladyer(SSL) provides you maximum online security.

Data Quality, Access, and Updating Personal Information

The Site will take reasonable steps to ensure that the Site’s information and data is complete, accurate, and timely for the user’s desired purposes. If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as email address), is inaccurate, or if a user no longer desires our services, the user should contact us to correct or update the information. 

Contact Information

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us by sending an e-mail. Please provide us with your name and e-mail address so we can service you quicker.

Please send your e-mail to: webmaster@goldbarsxxx.com
